<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Bryan Holman</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Bryan Holman</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 10:31:14 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Azure AI Fundamentals Study Guide</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/azure-ai-fundamentals-study-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 10:31:14 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/azure-ai-fundamentals-study-guide/</guid>
      
      <description>Below are questions to know the answer to pass the Azure AI Fundamentals (AI-900) exam.
Resources Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s official study guide for the exam. Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s official practice exam, which has 50 practice questions. I&amp;rsquo;d recommend taking it more than once. AI Overview What is artificial intelligence? Software that imitates human behaviors and capabilities.
What are the key ML workloads that Azure supports? Key ML workloads:
Custom machine learning Computer vision APIs Natural language processing Document intelligence Knowledge mining (search indexes) Generative AI What are challenges and risks specific to AI systems?</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using a Poetry environment in Visual Studio Code&#39;s Python Interactive window</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/using-a-poetry-environment-in-visual-studio-codes-python-interactive-window/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 16:04:14 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/using-a-poetry-environment-in-visual-studio-codes-python-interactive-window/</guid>
      
      <description>tl;dr – If you manage your project&amp;rsquo;s dependencies with Poetry, develop in Visual Studio (VS) Code, and use VS Code&amp;rsquo;s Python interactive window, you can use the poetry-monorepo extension to select your project&amp;rsquo;s poetry environment as the interactive kernel.
What is poetry? Poetry is a slick package builder and dependency manager for python projects. It helps project contributors specify and setup their Python environment.
Say you are working on a python project and need to incorporate a non-standard library, such as pandas.</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
