<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Bryan Holman</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Bryan Holman</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 16:04:14 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Using a Poetry environment in Visual Studio Code&#39;s Python Interactive window</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/using-a-poetry-environment-in-visual-studio-codes-python-interactive-window/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 16:04:14 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/using-a-poetry-environment-in-visual-studio-codes-python-interactive-window/</guid>
      
      <description>tl;dr – If you manage your project&amp;rsquo;s dependencies with Poetry, develop in Visual Studio (VS) Code, and use VS Code&amp;rsquo;s Python interactive window, you can use the poetry-monorepo extension to select your project&amp;rsquo;s poetry environment as the interactive kernel.
What is poetry? Poetry is a slick package builder and dependency manager for python projects. It helps project contributors specify and setup their Python environment.
Say you are working on a python project and need to incorporate a non-standard library, such as pandas.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Bryan</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/pages/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/pages/about/</guid>
      
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m a meteorologist turned data scientist.
In graduate school I studied how feature engineering and machine learning could improve wind forecasts–picking up Python, R, SQL, and data science along the way.
After graduate school I joined Kyruus Health, where I dove into data engineering, the cloud (GCP and AWS), dbt, and people/project leadership.
Currently I&amp;rsquo;m an AI Architect at Insight, where I design and build AI/ML-powered applications.
From five to nine I&amp;rsquo;m spending time with my amazing family, working out, playing sports, listening to instrumental rock, drumming, and enjoying all the Pacific Northwest has to offer.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resources</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/pages/resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/pages/resources/</guid>
      
      <description>Most of what I&amp;rsquo;ve learned during my career has been through on-the-job learning or self-study. The internet has a wealth of valuable content, one just needs to know where to find it.
Here I&amp;rsquo;ve collected the resources to which I refer the most.
Data analysis Packages:
Pandas for data analysis plotly for data visualization Data engineering Documentation:
dbt&amp;rsquo;s best practices GoogleSQL reference for BigQuery Machine learning/AI Courses:
Machine Learning Engineer learning path with Google Cloud Documentation:</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
