<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Bryan Holman</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Bryan Holman</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 10:31:14 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Azure AI Fundamentals Study Guide</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/azure-ai-fundamentals-study-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 10:31:14 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/azure-ai-fundamentals-study-guide/</guid>
      
      <description>Below are questions to know the answer to pass the Azure AI Fundamentals (AI-900) exam.
Resources Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s official study guide for the exam. Microsoft&amp;rsquo;s official practice exam, which has 50 practice questions. I&amp;rsquo;d recommend taking it more than once. AI Overview What is artificial intelligence? Software that imitates human behaviors and capabilities.
What are the key ML workloads that Azure supports? Key ML workloads:
Custom machine learning Computer vision APIs Natural language processing Document intelligence Knowledge mining (search indexes) Generative AI What are challenges and risks specific to AI systems?</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using a Poetry environment in Visual Studio Code&#39;s Python Interactive window</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/using-a-poetry-environment-in-visual-studio-codes-python-interactive-window/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 16:04:14 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/using-a-poetry-environment-in-visual-studio-codes-python-interactive-window/</guid>
      
      <description>tl;dr – If you manage your project&amp;rsquo;s dependencies with Poetry, develop in Visual Studio (VS) Code, and use VS Code&amp;rsquo;s Python interactive window, you can use the poetry-monorepo extension to select your project&amp;rsquo;s poetry environment as the interactive kernel.
What is poetry? Poetry is a slick package builder and dependency manager for python projects. It helps project contributors specify and setup their Python environment.
Say you are working on a python project and need to incorporate a non-standard library, such as pandas.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Bryan</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/pages/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/pages/about/</guid>
      
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m a meteorologist turned data scientist.
In graduate school I studied how feature engineering and machine learning could improve wind forecasts–picking up Python, R, SQL, and data science along the way.
After graduate school I joined Kyruus Health, where I dove into data engineering, the cloud (GCP and AWS), dbt, and people/project leadership.
Currently I&amp;rsquo;m an AI Architect and Engineer at Insight, where I design and build AI/ML-powered applications.
From five to nine I&amp;rsquo;m spending time with my amazing family, working out, playing sports, listening to instrumental rock, drumming, and enjoying all the Pacific Northwest has to offer.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resources</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/pages/resources/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/pages/resources/</guid>
      
      <description>Most of what I&amp;rsquo;ve learned during my career has been through on-the-job learning or self-study. The internet has a wealth of valuable content, one just needs to know where to find it.
Here I&amp;rsquo;ve collected the resources to which I refer the most.
Data analysis Packages:
Pandas for data analysis plotly for data visualization Data engineering Documentation:
dbt&amp;rsquo;s best practices GoogleSQL reference for BigQuery Machine learning/AI Courses:
Azure AI Fundamentals Azure AI Engineer Machine Learning Engineer learning path with Google Cloud Documentation:</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Study Materials</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/pages/study-materials/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/pages/study-materials/</guid>
      
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m an avid learner. It is something I do every day.
This is my process to learn and retain technical material as quickly as possible:
Read new material every day, for at least 30 minutes. Brainstorm questions that could be asked about the material as I read. Jot down the answers to those questions. Cite sources. The outcome is a lot of questions and answers that are great to review when studying for an exam.</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
